Guide to the Jaime Davidovich Collection MSS.155
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Video recordings
  - Clocktower, August, 1976; ID: 155.0165
    Duration: 30 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0165)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44210 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0164)
  - Sidewalk Copy 15 -- Silent Last Edit Fix, 1976; ID: 155.0177
    Duration: 11 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0177)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44214 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0177)
  - SoHo Television Presents: A Composite Tape, 1977; ID: 155.0279
    Duration: 21 minutes; Original format:3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0279)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44245 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0278)
  - 1. " Conscious Knocks Unconscious" 2. "Les Levine Interviewed by Steven Poser" 3. "Instant This Instant That" 4. Kipper Kids 5. "The Loner", 1977 - 1980; ID: 155.0237
    Duration: 1 hour 55 minutes; Original format: VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0237)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44234 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0236)
  - Tomorrow's Television Tonight, 1978; ID: 155.0195
    Duration: 58 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0195)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44220 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0194)
  - Interview with George Maciunas by Larry Miller, 1978; ID: 155.0219
    Duration:1hour 2 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0219)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44228 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0218)
  - SoHo Television Presents: John Cage Reads From 36 Mesostics Re and Not Re Duchamp, 1978; ID: 155.0228
    Duration:27 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy, cuid44191 (Box 39, Dvd 155.0228)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44231 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0227)
  - The Initiation of a New Composition for the Third Time/ By John Cage in Dialogue with Richard Kostelanetz, 1978; ID: 155.0243
    Duration: 28 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0243)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44236 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0242)
  - Out Reach: The Changing Role of the Art Museum, 1978; ID: 155.0246
    >Duration: 27 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0246)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44237 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0245)
  - Artists Cable Project Promo Tape / The Center For Non-Broadcast Television, 1979; ID: 155.0138
    Duration: 9 minutes; Orignial format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0138)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44201 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0137)
  - The Live! Show Promo, 1979; ID: 155.0312
    Duration: 22 minutes; Original format:3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0312)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44254 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0311)
  - Jaime Davidovich Promo Tape For Artist Television Network, 1979; ID: 155.0282
    Duration: 8 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0282)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44246 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0281)
  - The Live! Show 1. 12/21/1979 2. 5/28/1982, December 21, 1979; May 28, 1982; ID: 155.0105
    Duration: 55 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0105)
  - SoHo Television Presents: 1. " I Remember Beverly Hills" Ilene Segalove 2. "Bound Feet" Winston Tong, 1980; 1979; ID: 155.0234
    Duration: 54 minutes; Original format: VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0234)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44233 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0233)
  - The Ugly George Hour: Truth, Sex, and Violence, 1980; ID: 155.0189
    Duration: 30 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0189)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44218 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0188)
  - SoHo Wants to Know - Part I, 1980; ID: 155.0252
    Duration: 1 hour 2 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0252)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44239 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0251)
  - SoHo Wants to Know - Part II, 1980; ID: 155.0255
    Duration: 19 minutes;Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0255)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44240 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0254)
  - 1. Video Kitsch Commercial 2. Don Foresta On French Video Art (excerpt) 3. Still photographs, 1980's; ID: 155.0183
    Duration: 21 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0183)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44216 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0182)
  - Artists and Television Compilation Tape - Access Choices, 1980's
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0261)
    - Original Recording, cuid41447 (Box 19, U-matic 155.0015)
    - Preservation Master, cuid41448
      Duration: 49 minutes.
  - Dr. V. Tape 2, 1980's; ID: 155.0264
    Duration: 41 minutes; Original format: VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0264)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44241 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0263)
  - 1. Video Shop Collage 2. Opinion: Switching Channels; Public TV; Networks, 1980's; ID: 155.0267
    Duration: 11 minutes; Original format: VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0267)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44242 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0266)
  - Video Views from Iowa City #3, 1980's; ID: 155.0270
    Duration: 22 minutes; Origianal format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0270)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44243 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0269)
  - Access Choices #1, 1980's; ID: 155.0276
    >Duration: 58 minutes; Original format:3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0276)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44244 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0275)
  - Access Choices #2, 1980's
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0291)
    - Original Recording, cuid41445 (Box 20, U-matic 115.0037)
    - Preservation Master, cuid41446
      This recording contains sexual content.
      Duration: 34 minutes.
  - The Live! Show Goes International, 1980's; ID: 155.0285
    Duration: 25 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0285)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44247 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0284)
  - 1. Laurie Anderson: Conversations 2. Vito Acconci: Conversations 3. "Ursonate 1986"; "Anti-City"; My TV Dictionary: The Ball" by Hans Breder, 1980- 1986; ID: 155.0240
    Duration:1 hour 56 minutes; Original format:VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0240)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44235 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0239)
  - Adventures of the Avant-Garde, 1981; ID: 155.0207
    Duration: 10 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0207)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44224 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0206)
  - The Gap: Video Art By Jaime Davidovich And The Station, 1981; ID: 155.0294
    Duration: 16 minutes;Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copies (Box 39, Dvd 155.0294, Dvd 155.0295)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44249 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0293)
  - Raw Video: A Tribute To The Rock And Roll Trio, 1981; ID: 155.0309
    Duration: 27 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0309)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44252 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0308)
  - The Live! Show 1. 6/4/1982 2. 6/25/1982, June 4, 1982; June 25, 1982; ID: 155.0108
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0108)
  - Portrait of the Best Artist, 1982; ID: 155.0225
    Duration:6 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0225)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44230 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0224)
  - All Channels Cable in NYC, February 1982
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0273)
    - Original Recording, cuid41449 (Box 19, U-matic 155.0022A)
    - Preservation Master, cuid41450
      Duration: 64 minutes.
  - The Artist and Television -- Edited Version, 1982; ID: 155.0321
    Duration: 22 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0321)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44256 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0320)
  - The Live! Show 1. 9/17/1982 2. 1/14/1983, September 17, 1982; January 14, 1983; ID: 155.0111
    Duration: 56 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy, cuid44192 (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0111)
  - 1. Dr. Videovich Selected Works 2. (Fragment) The Live! Show, 1982; September 17, 1983; ID: 155.0132
    Duration: 48 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0132)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44199 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0131)
  - Public Access Choices Part 1, 1982; cuid44190
    - DVD Access Copies (Box 39, Dvd 155.0300, Dvd 155.0303)
    - Original Recording, cuid41443 (Box 20, Vhs 155.0046)
      Duration: 276 minutes; Preservation note: Last two hours of tape contain advertisements and were not digitized.
  - Public Access Choices Part 3 -- Stiff Show, Bible Speaks, Commercial Show, undated; ID: 155.0306
    Duration: 1 hour 4 minutes; Original format: VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0306)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44251 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0305)
  - The Live! Show Compilation Tape, 1982-1983; ID: 155.0135
    Duration:15 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0135)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44200 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0134)
  - The Live! Show - Selections, 1982-March 18, 1983; ID: 155.0315
    Duration: 59 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0315)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44253 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0057_p)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44255 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0314)
  - 1. Dr. Videovich Number One Art Lessons 2. Dr. Videovich Number Two Art Lessons 3. Dr. Videovich Number Three Art Lessons, 1983; ID: 155.0103
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0103)
  - The Live! Show 1. 1/21/1983 2. 1/28/1983, January 21, 1983; January 28, 1983; ID: 155.0115
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0115)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44193 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0113)
  - The Live! Show 1. 2/4/1983 2. 2/11/1983, February 4, 1983; February 11, 1983; ID: 155.0117
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0117)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44194 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0116)
  - The Live! Show 1. 2/18/1983 2. 3/11/1983, February 18, 1983; March 11, 1983; ID: 155.0120
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0120)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44195 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0119)
  - The Live! Show 1. 3/18/1983 2. 3/25/1983, March 18, 1983; March 25, 1983; ID: 155.0123
    Duration: 57 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0123)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44196 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0122)
  - The Live! Show 1. 4/1/1983 2. 4/29/1983, April 1, 1983; April 29, 1983; ID: 155.0126
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0126)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44197 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0125)
  - The Live! Show, May 20, 1983; ID: 155.0129
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0129)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44198 (Box Shared Fales PM 43, Digital betacam 155.0128)
  - The New York Art Parade Promo, September 27, 1983; ID: 155.0192
    Duration: 9 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0192)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44219 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0191)
  - "Buffalo Arts Profile" Presents "The Live! Show", 1983; ID: 155.0198
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0198)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44221 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0197)
  - Broadcast Coverage Art Parade, September 27, 1983; ID: 155.0201
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0201)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44222 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0200)
  - Special Presentation for the São Paulo Biennial, 1983; ID: 155.0213
    Duration: 47 minutes; Original format:3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0213)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44226 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0212)
  - Videoville Presentation by Dr. Videovich, June 29, 1983; ID: 155.0249
    Duration: 31 minutes;Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0249)
    - Presentation Master, cuid44238 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0248)
  - Metro Access Christmas Party, 1983
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0328)
    - Original Recording, cuid41455 (Box 17, Vhs 155.0259)
    - Preservation Master, cuid41456
      Duration: 61 minutes.
  - Evita: A Video Scrapbook, 1984; ID: 155.0186
    Duration: 14 minutes;Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0186)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44217 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0185)
  - The Live! Show - Cleveland, January 18, 1984; ID: 155.0204
    Duration: 37 minutes;Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0204)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44223 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0203)
  - TV On TV; Television Art For The 1980s Presents Saludos Amigos: Dr. Videovich Goes To Texas, 1984; ID: 155.0297
    Duration: 20 minutes; Original format:3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0297)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44250 (Box Shared Fales PM 47, Digital betacam 155.0296)
  - SoHo Television Presents: Artists Call Against U.S. Intervention In Central America, 1984; ID: 155.0318
    Duration: 29 minutes; Original format:VHS
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 147, Dvd 155.0318)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44257 (Box Shared Fales PM 48, Digital betacam 155.0317)
  - Study Corner Studio to 860, undated; ID: 155.0156
    Duration: 8 minutes; Original format: 1/2" Open Reel
    - DVD Access Copy (Box Shared Fales 148, Dvd 155.0156)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44207 (Box Shared Fales PM 44, Digital betacam 155.0155)
  - 1. Dean and Deluca 2. John Sanborn 3. Punk Art Opening, undated; ID: 155.0222
    Duration: 29 minutes; Original format: 3/4" Umatic
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0222)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44229 (Box Shared Fales PM 45, Digital betacam 155.0221)
  - Charles Simpson Interview About SoHo, undated; ID: 155.0231
    - DVD Access Copy (Box 39, Dvd 155.0231)
    - Preservation Master, cuid44232 (Box Shared Fales PM 46, Digital betacam 155.0230)
- Series V: Artifacts and Objects
  This series includes material artifacts collected by Jaime Davidovich. Subseries A: Fluxus contains a number of artifacts designed by Fluxus artists including boxes, wall paper, and stationery. Subseries B: Television Collection includes television shaped or themed artifacts including clothing, children's toys, and novelty items. Subseries C: ATN and The Live! Show includes objects connected to the production or administration of these media projects including Dr. Videovich's lab coat, an ATN seal paper embosser.
  - Subseries A: Fluxus
    - Partitioned box made of clear plastic containing, matches, rope, an electrical plug, a fishing hook, a glass shard, a pin, an x-acto blade, a bullet, and a ball bearing. Label fetaures an anatomically designed head, reads "a flux suicide kit by ben." Made by Ben Vautier., undated (Box 4, Folder 155.2.0005)
    - Flux Stationery, Hand in Glove. Shirk wrapped package of stationery, paper features a hand, palm up. Envelope features a black glove. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 6, Item 155.2.0007)
    - Flux Stationery, Hand in Glove. Shirk wrapped package of stationery, paper features a hand, palm up. Envelope features a black glove. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 7, Item 155.2.0008)
    - Flux Stationery, Foot in Shoe. Plastic shrink wrap enclosed stationery featuring a photograph of a foot. Envelope shows a shoe. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 8, Item 155.2.0009)
    - Flux Stationery, Torso in Fur Coat. Stationery set in skrink wrap plastic packaging. Photograph of a nude woman's body on paper, fur coat on envelope. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 9, Item 155.2.0010)
    - Flux Music Box. Plastic box containing two music box mechanisms. Two metal keys outside the box. Gear design label with object title on outside. Made by Joe Jones., undated (Box 4, Folder 155.2.0011)
    - Picnic Garbage Placemat. Placemat with black and white image of picnic remnants including banana peel, plate, crumpled napkin, watermelon rinds etc. Designed by Geoffrey Hendricks., undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 9, Item 155.2.0012)
    - Stomach Anatomy Apron. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 9, Item 155.2.0013)
    - Venus de Milo Apron. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Flat-file-folder 5 Left, Item 155.2.0014)
    - Flux Text, Revealing Fact. Flat plastic box with label reading "Revealing fact….hold finger on nipple one minute** then open box and read, a Flux-Test by Jock Reinolds". Thermometer affixed to inside lid, label reads "good person" and "bad person", undated (Box 4, Folder 155.2.0015)
    - Smoke Fluxkit. Clear platic box with partitions containing purple, pink, and yellow incense cones, two sticks of incense, leather, burlap, rope, dried orange peel, wood, cork, flexible plastic. Label features a black and white photographic image of a smelling machine used by a woman and a man. Designed by Yoshimasa Wada., undated (Box 4, Folder 155.2.0016)
    - Fluxgame Deck. White plastic box labeled "Deck by George Brecht a fluxgame" 64 cards, each with a different black and white design, hair photograph on reverse., undated (Box 4, Folder 155.2.0017)
    - Face Anatomy Mask. Square paper mask with eyeholes. Anatomy drawing with part of the face numbered and lettered. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 10, Item 155.2.0046)
    - Grotesque Face Mask. Square paper mask with eyeholes. Photograph of person's face with hands pulling the lips away from teeth to reveal very swollen gums. The Fluxus Codex indicates that the image comes from a book on dentistry and nutritional disorders. Designed by George Maciunas., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 11, Item 155.2.0047)
    - Photograph of model in Stomach Anatomy Apron. Black and white photograph on cardstock. Image of Pamela Kraft modeling the long version of George Maciunas' Stomach Anatomy Apron. [Identified Pamela Kraft using the Fluxus Codex although this photogrpah is not in the book.], undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 12, Item 155.2.0048)
    - Cluttered Desk Table Top. Square black and white photographic image of laminated photographic table top on cardstock. Table depicts a messy desk: telephone, notebook stapler, newspaper fragments, papers. Designed by Robert Watts and Peter Moore., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 13, Item 155.2.0049)
    - Crossed nude legs tabletop. Square black and white photographic image of laminated photographic table top on cardstock. Photographed by Robert Watts., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 14, Item 155.2.0050)
    - Giant Stamp Imprint Envelope. 9 paper envelopes with New York, NY postal meter mark on reverse. Designed by Robert Watts., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 15, Item 155.2.0051)
    - Meal Variation no. 7, eaten by Ferro. Black and white promotional photocard of laminated photographic table top. Image features an empty plate, two spoons, two forks, three knives, three glasses, cigarettes, matches, stamps, newspaper clippings, a photographs, and other odds and ends. Designed by Daniel Spoerri., undated (Box Shared Fales 041, Folder 16, Item 155.2.0052)
    - Assholes Wallpaper. Black and white phtoographs of [Yoko Ono's] butt. Same image printed twice. Designed by Ben Vautier., undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 8, Item 155.2.0053)
  - Subseries B: Television Collection
    - Green ceramic television container. Top lifts off, screen displays multicolored flowers and hearts. Made by Jaime Davidovich., 1978 (Box 26, Folder 155.2.0006)
    - Green plastic television with clear screen on black pedestal. Pedestal turns, rotating the two plastic figures inside the object. One is a girl wearing a red skirt, one is a man in a ablue suit. Price tag on the bottom indicates $1.50., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0018)
    - Sweatshirt with television design. Red, short-sleeved sweatshirt with multi-colored telvision designs. Size small, $15.00. Designned by Good Vibrations Inc., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0019)
    - Television set shaped alarm clock radio. Cat, bird and bomb design around digital clock face. Made by Tratron., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0020)
    - Television shaped snow-globe with soap opera theme. Clear plastic cube designed to look like a TV. Inside, male and female figures with thought bubbles. Hers, "Oh, John, I can Never be yours!" His: "I thought you were mine…Forever!" Pink, heart-shaped snow. Made by Enesco., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0021)
    - Musical Pocket TV. Red plastic TV with movign paper under the screen. Made by Sankyo Seiki Mfg Ltd., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0022)
    - TV fun-glasses. Plastic sunglasses shaped like televisions with green lenses. Made by Cathay., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0023)
    - Blue T-shirt. Reverse reads, "Don't Bother me…while I'm watching the game.", undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0024)
    - Ceramic television shaped clock. Made by Axis., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0025)
    - T.V. Star. Detachable plastic microphone attached to a TV shaped radio with strap. Made by Crown., undated (Box 26, Folder 155.2.0026)
    - Metal television shaped savings bank with removable lid. Made by Wagner's TV and Appliance., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0027)
    - Walking wind-up TV. Plastic TV-shaped figure with smiling face, arms, yellow shoes and mobile antenna. Walks when wound up., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0028)
    - Family in front of the television snow globe., undated (Box 25, Folder 155.2.0029)
    - Smurf Musicale color TV. Television shaped toy with wind-up music mechanism. Images move as the song plays. Made by Ohio Art Company, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 155.2.0030)
    - Television sunglasses with green lenses. In original packaging with Urban Outfitters pricetag, $3.00. Made by Accoutrements., undated (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0031)
    - Clear, plastic clip on tie swen with blue thread. The tie contains paper pictures of televisions and plastic miniatures of a coke bottle and a hungry-man TV dinner., undated (Box not specified, Folder 155.2.0032)
    - White, short slevved T-shirt with design of televisions, pink trashcans, downward pointing arrows, and a black bar-shaped graphic., undated (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0033)
    - Pink ceramic TV coin bank. Mirror screen, blue flower design over screen.Made by Vandor., 1981 (Box 27, Folder 155.2.0035)